Finding Aid for Gay Delanghe papers, 1961-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Gay Delanghe papers
1961-2006
Delanghe, Gay.
07152 Aa 2
Performer and professor of modern dance at the University of Michigan. Collection contains subject files relating to Delanghe's activities as a choreographer, dancer, teacher and department chair. Collection also contains photographs and audiovisual material documenting productions with which Delanghe was involved.
10 linear feet in 13 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Gay Delanghe (Donor no. 9737 ) and her estate in 2006 and 2007
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The collection is open to research.
Gay Ann Delanghe was born in Detroit, Michigan, in 1941. She attended Cass Technical High School in Detroit, graduating in 1958, and earned her bachelor's degree from the University of Michigan in 1962. She went on to complete a Master of Fine Arts degree in dance from UM in 1965, and then moved east to New York.
While in New York, Delanghe commenced her teaching career, joining the dance faculty at Barnard College, as well as serving on the faculty of the Connecticut College American Dance Festival from 1970 to 1973, and Interlochen National Music Camp starting in 1965. While at Barnard, Delanghe gained recognition for her interactive semi-spontaneous dance events such as Space Ruckus (1969). Alongside teaching, Delanghe maintained an active career as a performer and choreographer. From 1965 to 1972 she was a principle dancer with the Lucas Hoving Dance Company, touring extensively with this famed modern dance group. She also danced with other New York choreographers, including Yvonne Rainier and Janet Soares. Delanghe also actively created her own work during this New York period, such as Bomb (1969), Sidetrack (1969), Summer Dance 1-9 (1970), and Figures (1969), which were performed by Dance Uptown, The Dance Theatre Workshop, and the Lucas Hoving Company.
In 1972, Delanghe joined the Dance Department at the University of Michigan, recruited by her long-time colleague and then department chairman, Liz Bergmann. As part of the dance department, she was a founding member and organizational force for the Ann Arbor Dance Works (AADW), the residential faculty dance company, from 1984 to 2005. AADW served as a venue for many of her choreographed works, and through its active touring schedule, particularly in the 1980s, it brought her work to regional and national attention. In addition to AADW, Delanghe was also consistently engaged with the University Dance Company, the department's student performance company, as well as with various independent student productions, and graduate student projects.
Delanghe's departmental activities reflect her emphasis on dance pedagogy and educating students to become teachers. She taught courses in this area, and helped students to attain teaching practica in Ann Arbor area schools. She also organized the School of Education's accreditation of the Dance Department's teacher's training program, in which students could attain a teaching certificate along with their degree in dance. Many of her students went on to pursue active teaching careers in dance programs across the country.
During her tenure at Michigan, Delanghe remained an active performer and teacher in companies and venues around the world. In addition to serving on the Modern Dance faculty at Interlochen National Music Camp from 1965 to 1997, she taught during the summer at such institutions as Centre Formation Professionelle de Danse in Poitiers, France (1986, 1988), and Manhattenville College Jose Limon Summer Dance Residency in Purchase, NY (1977-78).
Throughout her career, Delanghe was an active promoter of the work of Lucas Hoving, reconstructing several of his major pieces after coming to the University of Michigan. In 1973 she staged Aubade with the University of Michigan Dancers in the Power Center. The following year she reconstructed Uppercase, and in 1990, she staged the acclaimed Icarus with the Ann Arbor Dance Works. The AADW took the performance on tour in 1992 with a performance at the Cunningham Studio in New York City.
Delanghe remained chair of the Dance Department until 2001 and continued to be an active faculty member and choreographer until her retirement in 2006. She died of cancer on August 1, 2006, at the age of 65.
The Gay Delanghe papers document a range of Delanghe's professional activities, with particular focus on choreography, teaching, and performing. The bulk of the records originate from the time of her graduation from the University of Michigan in 1965 through the first twenty years of her tenure in the University of Michigan Dance Department. There are few records from her childhood and college years, or from her late career. The records serve to illuminate her engagements as a dancer, and as a teacher, as well as the processes that went into her choreography and the staging of her work. In addition to this finding aid, a performance list exists which attempts to compile information on all of Delanghe's performances for which documentation exists in the collection. This list is available in Performance and Publicity series and upon request.
The collection is divided into ten series of materials relating to various aspects of the professional and artistic activities of Gay Delanghe. These series are: Biographical Materials, Choreography, Correspondence, Funding and Awards, Notebooks, Photographs, Programs and Publicity, Teaching, University of Michigan Department of Dance, and Audiovisual Materials.
Subjects:
Choreographers--United States.; Dancers--United States.; Delanghe, Gay.; Moderns dance.; University of Michigan. School of Music.; University of Michigan. School of Music, Theatre & Dance.; University of Michigan--Faculty.Faculty.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Choreography--Study and teaching.; Dance--Study and teaching.; Delanghe, Gay.; Delanghe, Gay--Performances.; Modern dance--United States.; Choreography.; Dancers--United States.; Modern dance--United States.
Genre Terms:
DVDs.; Videotapes.; Photographs.
- Biographical Materials
  The Biographical Materials series contains general records on Delanghe's career and educational background. These include her undergraduate and graduate diplomas, as well as resumes and her master's thesis A Choreography: Odyssey II.
  - Bachelor of Science Degree, University of Michigan, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut College, 1963 (Box 1)
  - "A Choreography: Odyssey II": Master's Thesis, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Master of Arts Degree, University of Michigan, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Memorials (Box 1)
  - Résumés (Box 1)
- Choreography
  The documentation of Delanghe's choreographic process is contained in the Choreography series. The bulk of this series consists of loose-leaf notes Delanghe produced in conjunction with her pieces. While the sets of notes are often titled, or have been given a title based on the title of their original folder, these may not be the official titles used later in performances. Folders are arranged alphabetically by title or working title. In some cases, these folders contain external materials Delanghe consulted while choreographing her dances. The series also contains notes on contemporary composers and musical genres.
  - Music (Box 1)
  - Notes
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - "Bach Horst (Allemande...)" (Box 1)
    - "Bill's Boogie" (Box 1)
    - "Blue Skies With Occasional Thunder From the Chairmen" (Box 1)
    - "Creation" (Box 1)
    - "Dangerous Kitchen" (Box 1)
    - "Dead Stream" (Box 1)
    - "Detroit-Er-Ella" (Box 1)
    - "Dinosaurs" (Box 1)
    - "Feather" (Box 1)
    - "Laura's Music" (Box 1)
    - "La Volta" (Box 1)
    - "Little and Big Fugue" (Box 1)
    - "Monk: Voices in Four Parts" (Box 1)
    - "Moore" (Box 1)
    - "Motor Tango" (Box 1)
    - "Murders", 2 folders (Box 1)
    - "Picasso Projects" (Box 1)
    - "Primordial Figures" (Box 1)
    - "Rampages" (Box 1)
    - "Red, Black, and White" (Box 1)
    - "Red, Red, Red" (Box 1)
    - "Schoenberg" (Box 1)
    - "Seven Deadly Sins" (Box 1)
    - "Sky Scenes" (Box 1)
    - "Small Monsters" (Box 1)
    - "Soldier's Tale" (Box 1)
    - "Statues in Motion" (Box 1)
    - "Talking Heads" (Box 1)
    - "Ten Little Indians" (Box 1)
    - "Three Gymnopedies for Bob Dunn" (Box 1)
    - "Two Fanfares" (Box 1)
    - "Two Sassie Bassie Rags" (Box 1)
    - "Vast Sky" (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1968-2006
  The Correspondence (1968-2006) series contains both incoming and outgoing departmental, professional, and personal correspondence accumulated throughout Delanghe's career. These materials range from requests for letters of recommendation, to letters of appreciation from audience members, to thank you notes from dancers appearing in her productions. They are arranged chronologically by year.
  - 1968-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - 1991-1999 (Box 1)
  - 2000-2006 (Box 1)
  - Undated, Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Funding and Awards, 1982-2002
  Funding and Awards (1982-2002) contains requests and applications for funding from both University of Michigan and external funding organizations. The funding proposals often contain information on the details of the proposed project, the technical specifications of productions, and the personnel involved, which is often missing from program notes and choreography notes. The series also contains the Arts Foundation Award (1989) and the Wayne State Arts Achievement Award (1982), which Delanghe received in appreciation of her contributions to the Michigan modern dance community.
  - Arts Foundation Award, 1989 (Box 1)
  - "Icarus,", 1992 (Box 1)
  - Lucas Hoving Video, 2002 (Box 1)
  - May Dance Institute, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Artist Award, 2006 (Box 1)
  - "Murders,", 1995 (Box 1)
  - "Satiana,", 1993 (Box 1)
  - Wayne State Arts Achievement Award, 1982 (Box 1)
- Notebooks, 1969-2005
  The Notebooks (1969-2005) series contains perhaps the most intimate glimpse into the artistic imagination of Gay Delanghe. These notebooks are filled with notes, sketches, and ideas collected in master classes, lectures, her own classes, and often spontaneously without explicit reference to a place or context. The notebooks are often dated and titled on the cover, but because they were used sporadically, sometimes with years in between entries, the titles can be misleading to the contents. In addition to Delanghe's writing on various subjects relating to dance and choreography, the notebooks also contain her unique method of notating movement through small stick-figure sketches. These remarkable drawings have utility in understanding the physical nature of the dance in question, but they also reflect Delanghe's much cited sense of humor and style. While the content and origin of the notebooks can be difficult to decipher, these records are important evidence of Delanghe's artistic identity.
  - Undated, 6 folders (Box 2)
  - "211" / "4 Lessons, Gps. For 211, 401/601", Summer 1996; Fall 1996; Fall 1997 (Box 2)
  - "211" / "Big Phrase List" / "Creative List,", Fall 2000 (Box 2)
  - "Alfredo Ballet" / Gittleman Comp," 173 (Box 2)
  - "Andre Gregory" / "Janet Comp." / "Junk Notebook,", 1980 (Box 2)
  - "Artwork,", 1970; 1978 (Box 2)
  - "Ballet: Alfredo, Maggie, Joe" / "Jazz: Marcia Siegal", 1972-1974 (Box 2)
  - "Ballet Collection,", Winter 1993 (Box 2)
  - "Beginners Modern," Spring 1978 / "Breaking Down Bach," Winter 1984 (Box 2)
  - "Black/Meyers,", Summer 1974 (Box 2)
  - "Children's Dance,", February 1971 (Box 2)
  - "Choreographic Production and Design" / "Notes on the Avantguarde,", Fall 1974 (Box 2)
  - "Classes,", 1974-1975; 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - "Classes" / "Nikolais,", 1977-1979 (Box 2)
  - "Classes/Teaching,", 1989-1998 (Box 2)
  - "Composition Schoenberg"/ "Lucas Muncie,", 1971 (Box 2)
  - "Composition,", Winter 1975 (Box 2)
  - "Dancing Motto" / "My God,", 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - "Danny Mccusker" / "Betty Jones" / "Me,", May 1989; February 1996 (Box 2)
  - "Gay Delanghe," Fall 2003 / "Duncan and Fokine," 2005 (Box 2)
  - "Gay Delanghe" / "Chris Dakin Graffman" / "Some Lesson Plans" / "Part of Primordial Figure,", 1979 (Box 2)
  - "Gem Classes-Lucas-Tour Beginners" / "Alfredo Connecticut Ballet,", 1972 (Box 2)
  - "Getting Comp. Ideas into one Book" / "Elements of a Good Dance,", May 1986 (Box 2)
  - "Going to the Market: A Sad Store"/ "Blue Sky Dance,", undated (Box 2)
  - "Icarus,", 2005 (Box 2)
  - "John Adams,", Summer 1995 (Box 2)
  - "Laban" / "Notebook for January", 1980; 2003 (Box 3)
  - "Lessons, Conn. College," Summer 1971 / "Lucas in Philly," 1972 (Box 3)
  - "Lucas--Children, Philly" / "Jamie Cunningham--Whitney,", 1972 (Box 3)
  - "Lucas: Masterclass, U of Florida; Raleigh, N.C.,", 1969 (Box 3)
  - "Lucas Technique; Lucas Improvisation; Class; Me Composition; Teaching Ideas," 19?? (Box 3)
  - "Maggie Black,", March 1974 (Box 3)
  - "Maggie Black" / "Children's Dance" / "Modern Classes" / "Laurie Anderson,", 1978 (Box 3)
  - "Modern Drama (Corrigan)", Winter 1974 (Box 3)
  - "Modern Tech.,", Winter 1999; Fall 1999; Winter 2003 (Box 3)
  - "Movement Explorations" / "Colby College Homemade Dance,", Spring 1975 (Box 3)
  - "Philly: 2 Classes Lucas,", 1971 (Box 3)
  - "Singing" / "Dancing," Fall 1975/, Fall 1976 (Box 3)
  - "Space,", December 1974 (Box 3)
  - "Stage Lite Design,", Fall 1972 (Box 3)
  - "Stage Movement + Comp.,", 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - "Teaching Composition,", Fall 1977; Fall 1980; Winter 1985 (Box 3)
  - "Technique" / "Floor work," Winter, 1984-1986; Winter 1999 (Box 3)
  - "Technique" / "Me Teaching" / "Corvino" / "Limon" / "Liz,", 1980 (Box 3)
  - "Theatrical Revelations, Musical, Dancable Choreocraps,", undated (Box 3)
  - "Water Nicks Material" Poitier, Winter 1986 (Box 3)
  - "Workbook," December 1986-1987 / "Labananalysis," 1995 (Box 3)
  - Untitled, Summer 1997 (Box 3)
- Photographs, 1961-2006
  The Photographs (1961-2006) in the Delanghe collection contain images of performances, rehearsals, studio portraits, as well as some non-dance related snapshots. They have been arranged based on content, where identifiable. Digital images are stored in CD format and are arranged separately from photoprint images.
  - Performances
    - "Album," UM Dance Department, 1980 (Box 3)
    - "All of a Feather," Ann Arbor Dance Works, 1988 (Box 3)
    - "Aristophanes: The Frogs," UM Dance Department, 1961 (Box 3)
    - "Assemblage," Lucas Hoving Co., 1969 (Box 3)
    - "Aubade," UM Dancers, 1974 (Box 3)
    - "Bergmann's Thesis,", 1963 (Box 3)
    - "Boleros," Choreoarte Dance Co. (Box 3)
    - "Bomb," Dance Uptown, 1969 (Box 3)
    - "Brace," David Dorfman (Box 3)
    - Connecticut College (Box 3)
    - "Dancemakers," University of Michigan, 1961 (Box 3)
    - "Dances for Two," Susan Matheke, Willie Feuer (Box 3)
    - Dancespace, San Diego, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Dance Uptown Album, Retirement Party, 2006 (Box 3)
    - "Duet," University of Michigan, 1976 (Box 3)
    - "A Gallery of Dances,", 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - "Icarus," Interlochen (Box 3)
    - "Icarus," Peter Sparling, Matthew Rose (Box 3)
    - "La Création du Monde," University of Michigan Dance Co., 1976 (Box 3)
    - "La Duncan and Fokine,", 2004 (Box 3)
    - "Little Fugue in G Minor," Ann Arbor Dance Theatre, April 26, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Lucas Hoving (Box 3)
    - "Move Around Memory," Dance Uptown, 1967 (Box 3)
    - "Murders," Interlochen (Box 3)
    - "Networks," Dance Uptown, 1967 (Box 3)
    - "Night and Day: Henry and Gay," Ann Arbor Dance Works, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Paradigm Dance Theater, Cathy Lichtman (Box 3)
    - "Pilgrimage," Ann Arbor Dance Theatre, 1964 (Box 3)
    - "QE2," Ann Arbor Dance Works, 2002 (Box 3)
    - "Satiana," Lucas Hoving Co. (Box 3)
    - "Satiana,", 1993 (Box 3)
    - "Seven Deadly Sins," University of Michigan Dance, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Rehearsal for "Seven Deadly Sins," University of Quebec, 1981 (Box 3)
    - "Sidetrack," Dance Uptown, 1969 (Box 3)
    - "Small Monsters,", 1985 (Box 3)
    - "Space Ruckus," Barnard College, 1969 (Box 3)
    - "Spirited Courtship: Lizzy's Revenge," Ann Arbor Dance Works, 1991 (Box 3)
    - "Statues in Motion," Ann Arbor Dance Works, 2002 (Box 3)
    - "Sun, Field, Two for Tea," Jackson Dance Council, 1974 (Box 3)
    - "Tanzmusik, 1997" (Box 3)
    - "Tears or Learning in the Living Room" (Prop), circa 1975 (Box 3)
    - "Toe/Ball/Heel,", 1974 (Box 3)
    - "Unit Scuttled," Interlochen, 1966 (Box 3)
    - "Uppercase," Lucas Hoving Co., 1969 (Box 3)
    - "Uppercase," UM Dancers, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Snapshots (Box 4)
    - Letter from Harriet Berg, 1960s (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - Retirement Party, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Studio Shots
    - Ann Arbor Dance Works (Box 4)
    - Gay Delanghe (Box 4)
  - University of Michigan Dance Department
    - Alana Barter (Box 4)
    - Carol Richards (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Students (Box 4)
  - Unidentified
    - Ann Arbor Dance Works (Box 4)
    - Barnard College (Box 4)
    - Contact Sheets (Box 4)
    - Interlochen (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - Negatives (Box 4)
  - Digital Materials
    - "A2 Dance Works Rehearsal," Tom Bower [Statuary: Classics in Motion], June 9, 2004; 4 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Photos: Gay's Piece," [Statuary: Classics in Motion, Ann Arbor Dance Works], June 9, 2004; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Gay Delanghe Photos Fr: UM Dance Dept." [Miscellaneous Studio Shots], 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Dances for Petersburg "La Duncan and Fokine" Choreography Gay Delanghe, Rehearsal," Tom Bower, February 1, 2004; 2 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Ann Arbor Dance Works," Tom Bower [Freeze Frame, Ann Arbor Dance Works], June 8, 2005; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Ann Arbor Dance Works: Gently Quirked: Choreography: Robin Wilson,", June 11, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Dances for Petersburg "La Duncan and Fokine," Tom Bower, February 2004; 2 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Ann Arbor Dance Works: Portraits," Tom Bower, June 11, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Ann Arbor Dance Works: Venice, Milan, Florence: Choreography: Gay Delanghe," Tom Bower, June 11, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "A2 Dance Works Selected Photos for Dance Magazine," Tom Bower, June 12, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Statues Project" [Images to be projected during performance], 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Ann Arbor Dance Works: The Dangerous Kitchen: Fertile Meaning: Choreography: Gay Delanghe," Tom Bower, June 11, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
    - "Freeze Frame" [Images to be projected during performance], 1 optical disks CDs (Box 4)
- Programs and Publicity, 1961-2005
  The Programs and Publicity (1961-2005) series contains all promotional material related to performances in which Delanghe took part, either as a dancer or choreographer. The bulk of these materials cover her post-master's degree activities in New York City and the first 15 years of her tenure at the University of Michigan (mid 1960s -- mid 1980s). These folders also contain reviews from publications such as the Ann Arbor News, Dance Magazine, The New York Times, and other regional newspapers. The majority of information gathered in the performance list, appended to this finding aid, stems from the records contained in this series. This list is also available in the first folder of this series.
  - Undated (Box 5)
  - The Dancemakers, June 9, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Ann Arbor Dance Theatre, January 9, 1964; January 18, 1964 (Box 5)
  - "Pilgrimage," "Intro," "Four Studies,", April 19, 1964 (Box 5)
  - "Little Fugue in G Minor,", April 26, 1964 (Box 5)
  - "My Fair Lady,", June 24-27, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Homestead Acres Theatre Camp, July, 1964 (Box 5)
  - "Regale," "Trio," "Harvest," "Clarion," "Regale in Reverse,", January 9, 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Pilgrimage," "By Chance," "More Haiku," "Madrigal,", March 11, 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Madrigal,", March 13-14, 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Quiet Noisy Dance,", May 15, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Interlochen, July-August, 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Odyssey II,", April 9, 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Much Ado About Nothing,", Fall 1965 (Box 5)
  - "Caracole," "Passings," "Intaglio," "Odyssey II," "Movie,", January 28-29, 1966 (Box 5)
  - "Regale," "Three Studies," "Odyssey II," "Clarion," "Trio," "Carcole,", May 12, 1966 (Box 5)
  - "Unit Scuttled," "move Around Memory," "Area,", February 4, 1967; 1967 (Box 5)
  - Interlochen, August 1967 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Rough In,", October 14, 1967 (Box 5)
  - "Comingoutandfivedancesforanoldmaid,", October 20-28, 1967 (Box 5)
  - "The Mind is Muscle,", January 13, 1968; April 11-15, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "She's Leaving Home,", March 22, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "She's Leaving Home,", April 1, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "She's Leaving Home,", July 15, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Z6508 Times,", July 15-August 21, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Icarus," "Rounds and Contrasts,", September 6, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Solo," "Quintet," "Satiana,", November 3, 1968; November 9, 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Bomb," "Sidetrack,", January 10-18, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Wall," "Figures," "Assemblage," "Satiana,", February 5, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Double Exposure Z6508 Times,", February 13-22, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Bomb," "Sidetrack,", February 16, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Wall," "Figures," "Assemblage," "Satiana,", February 22, 1969; March 5-7, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Eves,", May 11, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Uppercase,", August 15, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Space Ruckus,", November 14, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Uppercase," "Opus '69," "Satiana,", October 4-17, 1969; November 15, 1969 (Box 5)
  - "Bootlegger Battleback," March 27, April 4, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Uppercase," "Opus '69," "Satiana,", March 31-May 6, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Opus '69," "Satiana,", May 13-15, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Summer Dances 1-9,", June 25-27, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade II," "Uppercase," "Opus '69," "Satiana,", July 11, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Reflections,", August 7, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Almira" (Film), October, 1970 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Assemblage," "Uppercase," "Satiana,", January 22, 1971; February 8, 1971 (Box 5)
  - "Zip Code," "Assemblage," "Satiana,", July 31, 1971; August 1, 1971 (Box 5)
  - "Zip Code," "Assemblage," "Satiana,", August 14, 1971 (Box 5)
  - "Bodyshop I,", October 19, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Dance Uptown Spontaneous, Winter 1971 (Box 5)
  - "Tween Eight and Ten,", February 25, 1972; March 3-17, 1972 (Box 5)
  - "Girlie," "Staying On,", March 24-25, 1972 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade," "Uppercase," "Assemblage," "Satiana,", March 29-May 7, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Barnard Dance Concert, April 19-21, 1972 (Box 5)
  - "Staying On,", May 12-26, 1972 (Box 5)
  - "Homemade Dance,", December 8-9, 1972 (Box 5)
  - "Almira,", January 5-14, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade,", February 23-24, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Demonstration, March 15, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade,", April 6, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "The Leg and Thigh,", April 13-15, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Limbliteral,", June 13-14, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Limbliteral,", June 18-19, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade,", July 24, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Limbliteral,", November 29-30, 1973 (Box 5)
  - "Limbliteral,", January 31-February 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Three Studies," "Movie," "Regale,", February 15-17, 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Toe/Ball/Heel,", April 4-7, 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Sun, Field, and Two for Tea,", June 1, 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Aubade,", June 14, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Interlochen, 47th Season, August 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Uppercase," "De Profundis,", November 8-10, 1974 (Box 5)
  - "Tears or Learning in the Living Room,", February 8-9, 1975 (Box 5)
  - "Tears or Learning in the Living Room,", February 20-22, 1975 (Box 5)
  - "Homemade Dance or Body Exam,", March 8, 1975 (Box 5)
  - "Tears," "Yey I Wo Bayie,", April 4-6, 1975 (Box 5)
  - "Carmina Burana," "Seven Deadly Sins,", November 14-16, 1975 (Box 5)
  - "Elaborations,", February 29, 1976 (Box 5)
  - "Seven Deadly Sins,", March 19-21, 1976 (Box 5)
  - "Portraits,", June 10-12, 1976 (Box 5)